Damn it.
CHOI TAE-HO
MR. OH, HWANG YANG-JUNG
LEE DU-YEONG, HYEON-JU
Aren't you going home?
I was looking for a house, sir.
Jeez. It's not easy
finding a home nowadays.
What about your honeymoon?
My wife wants to go to Paris,
but I don't think we can go due to COVID.
Jeez. That damn COVID.
What brings you here at this hour?
Hey.
There's a big case.
I've been watching
a loan shark for about six months,
and this bastard takes videos
of people to threaten them with.
I got my hands on
a list of the bastard's victims today.
I'll share the data with you.
Let's dive into it together.
Yes, sir.
- Get back to it.
- Yes, sir.
Yes.
He said he received the list today.
He probably didn't do it alone.
Find out who took part in it,
and I'll pay you 100 million per person.
Yes, sir.
When will you get Oh In-muk's location?
I should be able to get the locations
of where he used his credit card
in the last seven days
by tomorrow morning.
I'll wire you the money
once I receive it. Good luck.
A hundred million.
How's it going?
Only Jang-do knew
the location of the hard drive.
The punk blurted it out
when President Choi nabbed him.
The bastards who were with him back then
fucking teamed up with Director Hong.
Myeong-gil.
Is there only one hard drive?
There's only one hard drive.
But everything's backed up
on a laptop we used
to transfer the videos to the hard drive.
I see.
For now, we should just stay put.
If we release that video
at the wrong time,
Director Hong, that son of a bitch,
is going to hit our company
with a tax audit.
Myeong-gil,
isn't it better to let them know
that you still have the video?
Scare them so they don't mess around.
You're smart, aren't you?
Shall we toast?
- Cheers!
ADDRESS, MART
GAS STATION, RICE STORE
GOHEUNG GROCERIES
Have you seen him?
I'm not sure. Customers wear masks,
so I'm not so sure.
I see. Is that so?
Fuck, seriously.
Take another look.
I don't know.
Think this is funny?
- Excuse me?
- You think this is fucking funny?
No, that's not it.
Goddammit.
Eyes down, you shithead.
Take a close look. Do you know him?
I don't know--
Do you know or not, you fucker?
Get up. Do you know him or not?
- I don't know.
- No?
Motherfucker, take a better look.
Do you or not?
Motherfucker.
- Fuck.
- I should kill you, you fuck.
Look at it closely.
Hello, sir.
Hello, welcome.
- Can I ask you something?
- Sure.
I'm looking for someone,
a friend of my dad's.
Yes, I know this person.
- You do?
- I do, but what's this about?
I'm getting married, so I wanted
to give him a wedding invitation.
I see.
Do you know his address?
Of course.
I deliver rice there every month.
Could I get an address?
Sure. I'll tell you.
BLOODHOUNDS
He's here.
Kang In-beom's profile.
I got everything
there is to know about him.
You work fast.
Speed is of the essence in these matters.
- Thank you.
- All right.
- It's done.
- Yes.
This is it?
Excuse me?
So you don't know.
Normally, when you make
someone do something like this,
you offer a token of thanks.
Right. How much should we give you?
All right, a lot.
I mean, we're a team
and family now. A big tip will do.
- Okay, here.
- Yes.
Thank you.
Call me whenever.
- Will do. Have a nice day.
- Goodbye, then.
All right.
TEN THOUSAND WON
Fuck, I meant a million won.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
KANG IN-BEOM
She told us not to use it.
But we should look
at his neighborhood on a big screen.
What if Da-min comes in?
She won't. She happened to be passing by
the last time we got caught.
A stroke of bad luck.
Hey.
- "Gangdong-gu, Seonggu-ro."
- "Seonggu-ro."
I told you she'd come. Turn it off.
What's wrong?
It smells like lonely men in here.
Why did you use it again?
Go to an Internet café.
We're sorry.
Also, sorry about the lonely smell.
Damn it.
Whatever. This room is ruined.
It's ruined.
Da-min!
- What?
- I'm sorry about today.
I'll take care of this smell.
How?
A diffuser.
A diffuser will get rid
of this sad old man smell.
Really?
First, to get rid of an odor,
one needs to find an opposing scent.
This sad old-man smell is
a blend of a thick, musky scent
with an unintended scent of rotten wood.
To get rid of it,
we need an opposing scent.
Something floral and fruity.
I use Baies from Diptyque.
- I like that one.
- That's good.
Hey, that's really good!
The fresh sweetness in the Baies
will cancel out
all the sad old man smell here.
We'll get you one
when we leave this place.
- A gift.
- Yes.
We'll get you one
for upstairs and downstairs.
For the bathroom too.
Okay, three it is.
Deal.
How does Kang In-beom know my number?
Look at this.
No way.
Something must be wrong, right?
What's wrong with Grandpa?
Who did this to him?
Well…
Hey…
Come to Four Garden shopping mall
in Incheon in an hour.
Call the cops, and the old man dies.
I'm going to fucking kill you.
Hey…
Da-min, you should tell us what he said.
He said to come to Four Garden mall
in an hour.
If we call the cops…
he said he'll kill Grandpa.
Hurry. There's no time.
- Gun-woo.
- Yes?
- How many do you think will be there?
- At least 30?
They'll probably have weapons.
Kang In-beom and that Mr. Jung guy
will be there too.
Should we call Gang-yong?
No, that would put Mr. Oh
in too much danger.
What about our senior?
Which senior?
Mr. Moon.
But he hurt his arm.
Wouldn't he help in any way he could?
Well, that's true, but…
Are you all set?
Yes, but Da-min, what's the bow for?
For rescuing Grandpa.
Absolutely not. It's too dangerous.
We'll go, just the two of us.
Step aside.
No, Da-min--
- What are you--
- Wait.
I can help in my own way.
I'm going, period. So don't stop me.
Come on. We don't have time.
Hey, she's a good shot.
Hey,
I think she'll be useful.
Sir, it's Woo-jin.
Mr. Oh
has been kidnapped.
Can you help us in any way?
I'm also indebted to Mr. Oh.
Don't go in without me, no matter what.
That's an order.
MOON GWANG-MU
734TH CLASS SENIOR
Junior Marines, you're here?
- Yes, sir.
- Sir, you've really gone all out.
I put some on because I had it
lying around at home. It itches.
I think it's old.
Get out before my skin
starts breaking out.
I'll go through the parking lot…
Who are you?
I'm here to rescue my grandpa.
She's Mr. Oh's granddaughter.
I see. Right.
You have similar facial structures.
It's been an hour.
Okay, but what's that bag?
It's a compound bow.
A guobaorou?
A compound bow.
Guo--
Sir, it's a bow for archers.
Right. Koreans are good at archery.
Is she good?
She is.
Okay. Archer and I will take
the stairs from the parking lot
and go to the top of the building.
Marines, you'll charge in
through the front gates.
We'll cover fire from the top. Understood?
- Yes, sir.
- Let's move.
- Follow me.
- Okay.
- This way.
- Right, okay.
Where is Mr. Oh?
Fucking kill them!
Fuck!
One, two, three!
Damn it.
- What?
- Where is it?
Where is it?
Whoa, Archer.
- Get them!
- Who is it?
Up there!
- Nice.
- Where?
What? What is it?
Hey, stop!
Up there!
The one in black, over there.
Who is it? Who's doing this?
The blue one, over there.
Damn it.
Keep helping the juniors, okay?
Hey, blue boy.
Were you on the track team?
Fuck.
Get lost!
Hey, he's coming! Make room!
Get him!
Damn it.
What are you doing? Get up.
Shit!
Damn it.
Shit.
You ain't shit without that knife.
Pull it out, motherfucker.
Pull it out!
You've got pride, don't you?
Come on, then.
Mister, are you all right?
Not at all.
One, two, three, four!
Hey, track guy!
Hey, asshole. We don't have time. Wake up!
Hey, where's Mr. Oh?
Look at this bastard,
giving his senior a scary stare-down.
- Archer, hand me an arrow.
- What?
It's fine. Give it to me for a second.
What a loyal bloodhound
we have here, this bastard.
I was like you, too,
when Mr. Choi was still in our midst.
Hey, do you know what becomes
of a bloodhound that's lost its master?
It becomes a stray
that just mauls anyone in sight!
No, you're fine.
You're just in shock. You're not in pain.
The real pain comes
when I pull this out!
Juniors,
please cover our archer's ears.
You're not married, right?
Well,
the most important thing
in the world is family.
But without this,
you'll never be able to make one.
Work or family. Pick one.
If you still choose work,
even in this situation,
I'll admit that you're a true pro.
But in exchange,
I'm going to puncture your balls.
Why?
Because I'm also a pro.
So, what'll it be?
I'll give you three seconds.
Three,
two,
one.
- Wait!
- What? Why?
I'll talk, sir.
Tuck in the head.
Get inside, hurry!
I said tuck in that head.
Sir, we'll go and save Mr. Oh.
Can you hold on to Kang In-beom?
What are you saying? I should come too.
We'll do it ourselves.
Sir, your arm's in bad shape.
Fuck, seriously.
Sir, Kang In-beom knows
where Kim Myeong-gil's slush funds are,
the location of the safe with the funds,
and where he hid Mr. Choi's gold.
Please get all that information from him
using your Marine spirit.
Please, sir.
All right, I'll do that.
Save Mr. Oh, no matter what.
- Yes, sir.
Let's go. Da-min, get in.
NATIONAL POLICE AGENCY
Here.
How does it look?
Sir, I've seen him standing next to
the Blue House Chief of Staff before.
- The chief of staff?
- Yes, sir.
That hooked nose and ears. I'm positive.
Why would a loan shark bribe
the presidential office?
Just being nosy?
Or he could be
a bigger player than we realize.
HEAVY DRINKER GUN-WOO
Hey.
Hello, I'm sorry for calling so late,
but we didn't know
what to do, so I called.
- What is it?
- Kim Myeong-gil kidnapped Mr. Oh.
So I'm heading
to Seoryeong with Woo-jin right now.
Just the two of you?
Why are you telling me this now?
I'm sorry, but they said
they'd kill Mr. Oh if we told the cops.
Hold on.
Did Kim Myeong-gil call you in person?
No, we captured one of his cronies,
and he told us.
So, you don't know for certain
whether Kim is there?
That's right.
Send me the location. I'll head over.
So don't go in, and wait for me.
Okay.
- Woo-jin, text him.
- Okay.
- Yes, sir.
- Hey, Jae-min.
Come to the meeting room now.
Yes, sir.
Jae-min, call in some backup.
It's Buseong-myeon, in Seoryeong.
It's about the case I mentioned last time.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
When did you see them?
About a month ago.
LIEUTENANT KIM JAE-MIN
Yes.
MR. KIM MYEONG-GIL
The cops are on their way.
Understood.
Hey, the cops are coming!
Start cleaning up!
All right.
Check if there's a back entrance.
Move out. Hurry up.
Turn off the engine.
Right.
Da-min, we'll see what the situation is.
Wait here.
We arrived before you and searched.
There's nothing. It's a flatfish farm.
Well…
Please talk to the bastard in the trunk.
Who's this bastard?
Kim Myeong-gil's goon.
The one who stabbed me.
I'm a cop, so answer me honestly.
Nod your head, you prick.
Is it Seoul Fish Farm?
Did anyone know we were coming?
Gang-yong.
This guy's cronies ran off mid-fight.
They might've given them a heads-up.
Leave this guy here,
and you guys get out of here.
You guys weren't here, okay?
- Okay.
- You aren't hurt, right?
- No.
Han-gu.
Where is Grandpa?
Let's wait.
The detectives will get back to us.
We don't have time.
We have to find him.
We will, no matter what.
You bastard, the safe!
Where is Kim Myeong-gil's safe?
Damn it, seriously!
Hey, asshole, you're really going to die
if you keep this up!
Give me a cigarette.
You bastard!
- Hit me!
- You're dead.
Hit me harder!
BEST PORK
BEOMSEUNG DISTRIBUTION
How'd it go?
What about Mr. Oh?
We couldn't find him.
I think those bastards
took him somewhere else.
Damn it.
Did he say anything?
That's one stubborn bastard.
He won't talk.
Having fun, aren't you?
- Want to see something more fun?
- What the hell is this fucker saying?
Damn it.
Sir! That bastard bit his tongue!
Fuck!
Come on, sir!
Damn it! Fuck!
- Hey!
- Fuck.
- Kang In-beom, snap out of it!
- Fuck!
- Woo-jin, call an ambulance!
- Okay.
Wait!
If we send him off,
how will we find Kim Myeong-gil's safe?
Still, we can't let a person die, sir.
If he dies, we won't get to the safe.
Damn it! Give it to me.
Help me get him down, please.
Sir, are you all right?
Sir, wake up! Are you okay?
Hello.
Where's the owner?
On vacation.
I see.
I'd like an iced coffee
with Ethiopian beans.
All right.
- Here. Please wait.
- Okay, thank you.
MY HAPPY FAMILY, I'LL KEEP YOU SAFE
CEO KIM MYEONG-GIL
ATTACHED FILE: 1 VIDEO FILE
Damn it!
Hey, Min-beom.
Kim Myeong-gil still has the video of me.
He just sent it to me.
What?
Hello?
Gang-yong?
Damn it!
Fuck.
Motherfuckers.
You motherfucker.
Sa…
What?
Salt!
Someone's been hit!
- She must be dead.
- Go check.
What happened?
- Call 911.
- I think someone died.
MR. OH
Gun-woo, come here. Hurry.
Hey, you dumbass punks.
Why are you causing a big problem?
What do you want?
Come to the fish farm at 9:00 p.m. today.
If you call the cops again, I'm going to
grind Oh In-muk up and feed the fish.
Answer me.
I've gotten rid of Min Gang-yong
and his cronies, so don't mess with me.
I said I'd kill your mom
if you showed up again.
See you there.
GANG-YONG
They got to Gang-yong? But he's a cop.
It'll be really dangerous this time.
We should go by ourselves.
Excuse me.
How long have you been there?
From the start.
Don't you dare leave me out.
I'm going to rescue Grandpa.
Come with me.
If something bad happens
to Mr. Oh in front of us,
Da-min's definitely going to
break down like Hyeon-ju.
Woo-jin, I never want to see that again.
But Gun-woo,
one thing's different from back then.
You know what that is?
Back then,
the invincible Marine duo was separated.
That's not the case now. And we're
a lot stronger, okay? Do you remember?
One, two, three, four, five.
One, two, three, four, five!
Yes.
So,
let's work together and save everyone.
Mr. Oh, Da-min,
and all the people that Kim hurt.
Why are we stopping?
Woo-jin and I will head in first.
You keep a lookout.
Come in once you find a spot to shoot.
Sounds good.
Get out.
Damn it. They dropped me off so far away.
Good thinking.
What?
You dropped her off far away
so she doesn't get hurt, right?
Well, I did that so we don't get caught.
Was it a bit far?
It'll take her ten minutes.
Let's finish this fast, just us.
Sounds good.
Kill them!
These bastards have a crap ton of weapons.
Woo-jin!
You son of a bitch!
Fuck!
Let go, damn it!
Let go!
Fuck!
Son of a bitch!
Hey, you fucker!
What the hell?
Son of a bitch!
Hey, you son of a bitch!
Fuck!
Hey.
You can't even get rid of two kids?
I'm sorry, sir.
You're always fucking apologizing.
Now then.
Stop!
Hey!
You punks so much as move a muscle,
and I'll slit his throat,
so do what you will!
That's right. Stop moving.
What are you doing, you stupid fucks?
Hurry up and kill them.
Should I kill them?
You sons of bitches are unbelievable.
Duck!
- What's that?
- What happened?
You asshole! Come here!
I said, kill them already!
You sons of bitches!
What are you doing? Let go, you prick!
- Let me go!
- Let's go to the hospital.
Kill them! Come on!
Grandpa! Are you all right?
It's me, Da-min.
You plucked my eyebrows.
Mr. Oh, are you all right?
Thank you.
What's this?
Move faster.
Hurry up and get to work!
Who is it?
Chinese delivery.
What the hell, you bastards!
Stay still, you fucking bastard!
Search the entire area!
- Scour every inch!
- What is this place?
I found it! Everyone over here!
- Those bastards…
- What were they doing here?
I'm Yang Yun-seo
from Major Crimes Investigation Division.
Here's a search warrant.
We'll now be conducting
a search and seizure on your property.
We appreciate your cooperation. Come in.
Hurry up inside.
Mr. Kim Jae-min?
You're under arrest
for murder, bribery, and other charges.
Fuck. What a shitty day.
Let's go.
- Sir.
- Yes.
The warrant was issued quickly,
so we went into Kim's house.
Several phones were found
in his closet drawer.
We traced the numbers. They all belonged
to dead or missing individuals.
Jeez.
This crazy bastard kept the phones
of the people he killed.
He can't get out of this one.
Not even the US president could save him.
What about fleeing overseas?
He's a wanted man now,
so it won't be easy.
People often flee to China on cargo ships.
Kim is a grade-A wanted criminal.
We'll focus surveillance
on potential stowaway routes.
He won't escape Korea.
But it's not completely impossible.
You all seem to think this is all over,
but I'm really on edge right now.
That bastard still has that video of me.
If he loses it and releases it,
it's over for me.
Gang-yong.
I have to see that bastard behind bars.
Min-beom.
I understand.
But look at Han-gu's condition right now.
And Tae-yeong isn't conscious yet.
We'll need some time.
We'll help you.
It's not over until it's over.
Can you find us Im Jang-do's whereabouts?
Why Im Jang-do?
Im Jang-do's probably hiding somewhere,
trying to stay away from Kim Myeong-gil.
But I think Im Jang-do may know
where Kim Myeong-gil might run off to.
Right, Im Jang-do may have given him tips
on how to smuggle out.
He mentioned
he was in charge of stuff like that.
Okay, I'll look into it.
How much is it in cash?
I can bring it down to 18 million.
Im Jang-do hasn't used a phone or card
under his name in the last six months.
He avoided everything that was traceable.
Is there any other way?
Well, all we've managed to find
for now is his bank account number.
And the last transaction was
a cash withdrawal in March in Suwon.
Isn't that enough to find him?
There are a few months' worth of footage,
so we'd need a man on it full-time.
It would take some time.
Could we get his account number?
This prick is probably strapped
for cash right now.
Now wire money into that account.
When you send it, put down
your phone number under the sender's name.
Then he'll contact you. Guaranteed.
- How much should I send?
- A large amount should do.
Ten thousand won?
I wondered
if I should've mentioned this last time,
but in this line of work,
the meaning of "large amount" varies.
That large amount from when I got you
Kang's personal details
was supposed to be a million,
not ten thousand.
A million won?
Of course, I don't mean
to ask for that money now.
I'm not some cheapskate.
We're family, after all.
In our situation,
how much are we talking about?
He's going to scoff at a million won.
Ten million won.
He'll bite right away.
Your wounds aren't healing
because you keep drinking alcohol--
Fuck!
- Doctor.
- Yes, sir.
Just do your job.
Yes, sir.
Fuck.
Sixty-six,
sixty-seven,
sixty-eight, sixty-nine.
Woo-jin.
There's no number.
Hello?
You're the kid
that was with President Choi, right?
I am.
And the cops told you my account number.
What is it? Why did you send the money?
Kim Myeong-gil is on the run.
Why's that?
Police raided Kim Myeong-gil's house
and found evidence that he killed people.
When was that?
Two days ago.
You know where he'll flee to, don't you?
I do.
Please.
We want to catch Kim Myeong-gil. Help us.
How much will you pay?
A large amount.
Shit, you've got to be fucking kidding me.
- A billion!
- A billion?
I trusted President Choi
and got fucked over.
I deserve that much compensation.
But right now, we only have--
In four days, Kim Myeong-gil will flee
overseas using the method I taught him.
You know my account, right?
Think it over.
This is ridiculous.
How will we get a billion?
Should we ask Mr. Oh?
Mr. Oh doesn't have money.
The money he gave us
was the last of the funds.
Hold up.
How much is in there?
I think around 300 million.
It's nowhere enough.
Should we ask Min-beom?
Im Jang-do's the one
who took that video of Min-beom.
You think he'll help us with this?
Still, Min-beom's the only one
with that kind of money.
Let's ask him just once, okay?
Sir, here they are.
Do you guys trust Im Jang-do?
Well,
we do think we can trust
the information he has.
What if he takes the billion
and hightails it overseas?
Then what do we do?
If Im Jang-do breaks his promise and runs,
we'll chase him down until we catch him.
That much I can promise you.
You keep that promise.
- I will.
- Okay.
1,000,000,000 RECEIVED
Okay, I'm done checking. Move along.
Okay.
You may go.
UNKNOWN CALLER
Write this down.
The day after tomorrow, at 1:00 a.m.,
a ship named Nike will depart from Pohang
for Ho Chi Minh City.
Kim gave political funds
to a high-ranking Vietnamese official.
He's going to take off
with all of his slush funds.
The container number is TJBU 9004230.
His funds will be hidden in a truck
inside the container.
Should we go for it
when he's getting on the ship?
It's a big ship,
so it won't be easy to find.
How do we find it?
Get on the ship with him!
You mean all the way to Vietnam?
Well, that's up to you.
- I'm hanging up now.
- Wait.
What should we do
if we want to board that ship?
I'll text you a contact. Tell him
I sent you, and try to work out a deal.
FYI, he likes cash.
We got the text.
I didn't know what you'd need,
so I prepared a bit of everything.
Thank you, sir.
Take care of yourselves.
Yes, sir.
Okay?
Let's go up.
You go on ahead.
I need to talk.
All right.
Thank you for all your help.
We should be thanking you.
See you, Da-min.
See you.
Go ahead.
You know my number, right?
Let's go.
- Yes, Min-beom.
- Are you on your way?
We're on our way.
Don't get hurt, okay?
Okay.
Gang-yong and I
will take care of the rest.
Drive safe.
Okay.
Let's hurry.
Just a second.
Woo-jin.
Okay.
Set sail.
Let's check the inside first.
Kim Myeong-gil!
Damn it.
Yes.
If you ever show up again…
I'll kill you.
Gun-woo.
Are you all right?
What is it?
Woo-jin.
I think I've become a bloodhound.
Gun-woo, have you forgotten
about the heart of a boxer?
We just have to find our way back.
Okay? Let's go back together.
Okay.
Let's go back.
Here.
Whoa! Woo-jin!
Man, we found it!
Hey.
- Min-beom, where are you?
- I'm almost there.
Did you find the gold bars?
Yes, we found them all.
And the phone?
I'll go get it.
- Woo-jin, here.
- Right.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
How'd things go?
I finally got the phone.
They did a good job.
I asked Interpol for backup.
They'll be waiting in Vietnam.
It's all over.
You really went through a lot, kiddo.
Thanks, Gang-yong.
What would you guys like to do?
Mr. Choi always wanted to help the poor
get proper medical treatment,
so I'd like this money to be used
in accordance with Mr. Choi's wishes.
Well, what do you think?
You don't want the money for yourself?
Well, of course, I do.
But this isn't my money.
I've only paid back Mr. Choi
for his kindness
and kept my promise to him.
Okay.
Guys.
We have a total of 168 golden bars,
weighing seven kilograms each.
Each one is worth 500 million won
at spot price. About 84 billion in total.
If you want, I'll take this
and start a welfare foundation
under Iil Group.
Through that foundation, we'll be able
to provide medical help to those in need.
Or should I just have
our company add some money
and set up a hospital?
- That sounds like a great idea.
- Right?
It does.
I think my dad will like it.
And I think it'll help
with our corporate image.
Besides, we'd be doing the world good.
I'll get started on it
once I'm done with the hotel.
Min-beom, could you include
Mr. Choi's name in the hospital name?
- What was his name?
- It's Choi Tae-ho.
To be honest, it won't be easy,
but I'll consider it.
Thank you.
What?
I'll cover the missing amount
with my own money.
Think of it as a bonus
for a job well done.
It's all right. I'm really okay.
Mr. Choi would have done the same.
Take it.
Don't know what to say?
A thank you would do.
Thank you, Mr. Choi.
No.
I should be thanking you.
Thank you so much.
Catch!
- No!
- Here we go!
- I'll be here.
- There, okay?
I'll be here.
This one too.
Hey, Gun-woo.
You're where?
Hey! Gun-woo!
My dear son.
Woo-jin.
What happened to your face?
You went through so much.
It's all over, Mom. Let's go home.
All right.
I'm so proud of you boys.